{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"The%20Harvard%20architecture%20for%20micro-controllers%20added%20which%20additional%20bus%3F","correct_answer":"Instruction","incorrect_answers":["Address","Data","Control"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In%20the%20original%20Star%20Trek%20TV%20series%2C%20what%20was%20Captain%20James%20T.%20Kirk%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Tiberius","incorrect_answers":["Trevor","Travis","Tyrone"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In%20Grand%20Theft%20Auto%20V%2C%20what%20was%20Michael%20De%20Santa%27s%20former%20surname%3F","correct_answer":"Townley","incorrect_answers":["De%20Santos","Watson","Simpson"]},{"category":"Science%3A%20Computers","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20does%20the%20acronym%20CDN%20stand%20for%20in%20terms%20of%20networking%3F","correct_answer":"Content%20Delivery%20Network","incorrect_answers":["Content%20Distribution%20Network","Computational%20Data%20Network","Compressed%20Data%20Network"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"On%20the%20show%20%22Rick%20and%20Morty%22%2C%20in%20episode%20%22Total%20Rickall%22%2C%20who%20was%20a%20parasite%3F","correct_answer":"Pencilvester","incorrect_answers":["Beth%20Smith","Summer%20Smith","Mr.%20Poopy%20Butthole"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In%20Need%20for%20Speed%3A%20Most%20Wanted%20%282005%29%2C%20what%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20main%20antagonist%3F","correct_answer":"Clarence%20%22Razor%22%20Callahan","incorrect_answers":["Hector%20%22Ming%22%20Domingo","Toru%20%22Bull%22%20Sato","Karl%20%22Baron%22%20Smit"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"%22Minecraft%22%20was%20released%20from%20beta%20in%202011%20during%20a%20convention%20held%20in%20which%20city%3F","correct_answer":"Las%20Vegas","incorrect_answers":["Paris","Bellevue","London"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20many%20regular%20Sunken%20Sea%20Scrolls%20are%20there%20in%20%22Splatoon%22%3F","correct_answer":"27","incorrect_answers":["32","30","5"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"All%20of%20these%20maps%20were%20in%20%22Tom%20Clancy%27s%20Rainbow%20Six%20Siege%22%20on%20its%20initial%20release%3A%20House%2C%20Clubhouse%2C%20Border%2C%20Consulate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20%22Kingdom%20Hearts%22%2C%20who%20abducts%20Jasmine%20in%20the%20Lamp%20Chamber%3F","correct_answer":"Riku","incorrect_answers":["Riku%20Replica","Xaldin","Captain%20Hook"]}]}